http://www.bestturkishfood.com/en/privacy-notice

Wishlist
(0)
My Account
(0)
items
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Privacy Policy
BTF understands your concerns about how your private information you have supplied and we gathered is used and shared. BTF respects your privacy and appreciates your trust in our company in this issue. This notice describes our privacy policy and how your private information is protected and used.
Information Collection: We collect information on a voluntary basis from customers and visitors to our site, when they choose to register or place an order with us. To ensure easy shopping and timely product delivery we ask for information including your name, address, email address, phone number and credit card information (for your protection we only display the last four digits of your credit card). All of these are necessary for purchase and quick communication with you about the status of your order. Should you wish to change your information, simply click on My Account link located on the top of the Home Page. In addition, bestturkishfood.com will collect information including Browser Type, IP address, and server information from consumers who write to us about technical problems. In addition, we collect aggregate information on pages visited, and information volunteered by consumers, such as survey information and/or site registrations.
Information Use: Persons and customers who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online to ensure quality service. People who register and specify that they wish to receive telephone calls in regards to new products and services or upcoming events, or in connection with surveys conducted by us or on our behalf may receive calls from time to time.
The information we collect is only used to (1) improve the content of our web site, customer service, and provide technical support (2) customize the content and/or layout of our page for individual consumers, and (3) contact consumers about updates to our web site and for marketing purposes, such as improving BTF services or alerting customers of special offers and events. This information is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. This means we will not distribute, sell or rent your name or personal information to any third party. If you are registered, you may remove your name from our lists by updating your account information. You will be prompted with a choice upon registering with BTF.
Sharing of Information: Bestturkishfood.com DOES NOT SHARE OR SELL ANY PERSONAL OR FINANCIAL INFORMATION other than situations stated below:
Credit Card transactions:When using a credit card to make a payment, BTF is required to provide certain information to the credit card processing gateway. The information we provide is required to authorize the credit card transaction and will be solely used to complete the order. The information we submit is your name, last name, street address, zip code, city, country, e-mail address, order amount, credit card number and expiration date of credit card.
Legal Requirements:Legal authorities may request your personal information in rare cases. Under those circumstances BTF may provide requested information to legal authorities as defined by law.
Updating Personal Information:Your name will be removed from our email list if you request not to be contacted for future promotions and/or not to be contacted for research purposes by bestturkishfood.com. You may remove your name from the email list and edit your personal information from our computer system by updating your account information.
If you use this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password, for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password.
Children Use:Our web site does not contain any adult or offensive material. If you are under 18, you may use our services only with involvement of a parent or guardian. Bestturkishfood.com reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, or cancel orders at their sole discretion.
Cookies:Cookies are combination of strings and numbers that identifies your visit to our site. As http is a stateless protocol it is not possible to establish a connection between two visits of a customer to our web site. That means cookies are required in our web site to implement the shopping cart and personalize your experience in your next visit. Although we use cookies, we are not storing any personal information on cookies. Both session and non-session cookies are used by BESTTTURKISHFOOD.com to enhance your shopping experience. Saving carts, shopping lists, addresses, and setting personal preferences are all features made possible by the use of cookies. By accepting cookies, you can take full advantage of our site shopping experience. Should you wish to trace cookies or disable them, please see the "help" section of your browser. Please be aware that disabling cookies will prevent you from shopping with us.
Security:To protect our members, we use latest technology to encrypt the information you send us when you place your order. The information is encrypted on your computer, sent through the Internet as encrypted code, and decoded on bestturkishfood.com’s secure server. It cannot be read in transit. The information we store on our server is protected by firewalls and intrusion detection systems. Only authorized personnel have access to that information with certain restrictions.
Policy Changes and Miscellaneous Information: By visiting our web site bestturkishfood.com you are accepting our privacy policy described in these pages. If you do not agree with our terms, it is your responsibility in full to use our website and services.We intend to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted here. If a person wishes to monitor changes in this policy, he/she should check this page for updates periodically. Please contact our Customer Satisfaction Center at service@bestturkishfood.com, if you have any questions about our privacy policies or any other policies.
Sign up for our newsletter
Wait...
Copyright © 1999 - 2020 Best Turkish Food. All rights reserved.
